这玩意儿显然没用
Well, that thing's clearly in the way.
是啊 啊哈
All right. A-ha. Heh.
死冰箱
Damn fridge!
- 嗨 乔伊 你好吗？ - 很好
- Hi, Joey. How you doing?     - Great...
- 室友   - 啊
- roomie.     - Ah!
- 我们现在的确是室友   - 没错 经你提
- Yeah, I guess we are roommates now.     - I know. Now that you bring it up...
我们的冰箱坏了 得买台新的
uh, our fridge is broken. We have to get a new one.
我打听过 你分一半 得出四百元 感激不尽
I checked around and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
我才不跟你分一半
I'm not paying for half of that.
我只住到我们那边整理好
I'm only staying here until my apartment gets fixed.
瑞秋 这台冰箱是我出生之后 我父母买的
Look, Rach, my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
我用都没问题 你一来它就坏了
Now, I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
这意味着什么？
What does that tell you?
冰箱无法和人一样长寿
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
好 你也知道自动提款机 一次只能提三百元
All right, you know that the ATM only lets you take out 300 at a time...
剩下的一百我就收支票
so I'll take a check for the other 100.
你在开玩笑吧？
Heh. You're joking, right?
那当然 我不收支票
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
幸好你很帅
Thank God you're pretty.
老友记 第六季 第十九集
（中央咖啡厅）
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey!     - Hey.
你们有认识的帅哥吗？
Hey, do you guys know any cute guys?
当然有 就是我的好朋友乔伊
Well, of course, I do. My good friend, Joey, over here.
我忘了...谢谢你 钱德
Oh, I'm sorry. Thank you, Chandler.
周末有大型慈善晚会 罗夫罗兰买了一桌
Anyway, there's a charity ball this weekend and Ralph Lauren bought a table...
我也得去
so I kind of have to go.
- 为什么慕款？ - 不晓得
- What's the charity?     - I don't know.
不是某种树就是某种病...
Something, either trees or disease, I...
- 罗夫很会碎碎念   - 罗夫都趁你
- Ralph mumbles a lot.     - Does Ralph mumble...
- 不专心时碎碎念吗？ - 对呀 好奇怪
- when you're not paying attention?     - Yeah. It's weird.
总之我得找个男伴
But the thing is, I need to find a date.
你想找什么样的人？
What kind of guy are you looking for?
自己有晚礼服或租得起晚礼服
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
所以必须是男人 身家起码要有50元
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
只差一点
Ooh, so close.
- 大家好   - 嗨
- Hey, everybody.     - Hey.
- 这是伊丽莎白   - 嗨
- Uh, this is Elizabeth.     - Hi, Elizabeth.
- 我就是那个学生   - 哈哈哈
- I'm the student.     - Ha-ha-ha.
真可爱对吧？才怪
Isn't she cute? Nope.
也许我不该多嘴 但你们在一起
This is none of my business, but weren't you guys supposed...
- 不是不能被看到？ - 我们没有在一起
- to not be seen in public together?     - Oh, we're not together.
没有 我们只是两个
No. We're just two people who happen to have run into each other...
在咖啡馆巧遇的人
here at the coffee house. Heh, this is...
真奸诈
Oh, sly.
我很想多认识你们 但是我得走了
I really wanted to meet you guys, but I have to run.
- 改天见   - 好
- I'll see you later?     - Okay.
- 罗斯 再见   - 再见
- Bye, Ross.     - Bye. See you.
- 我不是故意撞到你的 先生  - 没关系 女士
- Didn't mean to run into you like that, sir.     - That is quite all right, ma'am.
拜
Bye.
她为什么要走？刚放学功课一大堆？
So why's she leaving? Is it a school night and she has a lot of homework to do?
对 她明天要交 分子流行病学报告
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
帮我祝她好运
Well, tell her "good luck" with that.
还有吗？别客气
Anyone else, huh? Bring them on.
- 她什么时候生日？ - 我不知道 瑞秋 为什么问？
- Oh! When's her birthday?     - I don't know, Rachel. Why?
我好久没吃儿童生日餐了
Well, you know it's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
- 我喜欢伊丽莎白   - 谢谢
- I like Elizabeth.     - Well, thanks.
我真的很喜欢她 叫她今年早点送女童子军饼干来
In fact, I like her so much that you tell her I want my cookies early this year.
我要薄荷巧克力饼和巧克力派
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
你们别闹他了 说真的 你们交往得怎样？
Guys, give him a break. Ross, seriously, how's it going with her?
非常好
Well, it's actually been great.
她才20岁 还不想太认真
She's 20, so she's not looking for anything too serious...
最适合现在的我
which is perfect for me now.
太好了 她真的好像很不错
Well, that is great. And seriously, she seems very nice.
谢谢 我知道你们想让我难受
I know you guys like to give me a hard time...
但我真的很希望你们能喜欢她
but it means a lot to me that you like her.
- 只要知道你们...   - 我想到个很棒的
- Just knowing you guys are, like...     - Okay, I got a good one.
好
Okay, um... Heh.
她是才12岁吗？
What is she, like, 12?
钱德 你觉得我们的沟通够吗？
Chandler, do you think we talk about our relationship enough?
够 有水果卷吗？
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll Ups?
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hey.
好 我刚想到一个人 很适合当瑞秋的男伴
Okay, I just thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
有意思 我们也找到人了
That's so funny, we found someone too.
那好 她可以在我的人 和你们的怪胎之中选一个
That's good. I guess she'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
- 为什么我们的人是怪胎？ - 因为你们的品味就是那样
- Why would our guy be a weirdo?     - Because that's just your taste.
瑞秋才不会选你的蠢人
See, Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
- 是吗？ - 没错
- Oh, yeah?     - Yeah.
我这个是律师 还当义工
My guy is a lawyer who does volunteer work.
而且他有这个东西
And he has one of these.
脸屁股？
A face ass?
- 酒窝啦   - 我们这个是钱德的同事
- A chin dimple.     - Well, uh, our guy works with Chandler.
人好聪明又会打扮
And he's really nice and smart and he's a great dresser.
- 你们看过他的身体吗？ - 没有 他是一颗飘来飘去的头
- Have you seen your guy's body?     - No. Our guy's just a floating head.
我这个身材很赞 他是我的按摩客人
Well, my guy is spectacular, okay? He's a massage client.
有一次他在按摩台上 就被我看光光了
And one time, um, when he was on the table, I looked at it. And I mean, all of it.
- 你不是不能偷看吗？ - 报警来抓我啊
- You're not supposed to look.     - Yeah, like there are police for that.
- 你会偷看？你给我按摩过   - 没错
- What, you look? You massaged me.     - I know.
好 你那个或许身材很好 但我们这个
All right, your guy may have a great body, but our guy...
- 很风趣   - 钱德式的风趣？
- is really funny.     - Chandler funny?
- 我们这个舞功高强   - 我这个饱读诗书
- Our guy's a great dancer.     - My guy's well-read.
- 我们这个发质很好   - 我这个牙齿漂亮
- Our guy has great hair.     - My guy has great teeth.
我们这个香的不得了
Our guys smells incredible.
你真这么哈他？
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你的脸色不太好 乔伊
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
冰箱坏了 我得把东西都吃掉
Well, the fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
冷盘 冰淇淋 莱姆...
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
嘿 咖啡色罐子里的是什么？
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
- 那个还在？ - 已经不在了
- That's still in there?     - Not anymore.
总之你要怎么付钱给我？
Ahem, so, anyway, how do you want to pay me?
你要提供某种服务吗？
Is this a service you're providing me?
不是 是我要买冰箱 我们的新冰箱
No, for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
我们的新冰箱？
Our new fridge?
- 我已经不住这里了   - 那又怎样？
- I don't live here anymore.     - So what?
假设我们是离婚夫妻
Look, okay, suppose we were a, uh, divorced couple.
- 嗯哼   - 我取得孩子的监护权
- Uh-huh.     - And I got custody of the kid. Right?
结果孩子死了 我总得买个新孩子
Now, suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
好
Okay.
给我四百元
Give me $400!
- 盖勒教授？ -嗯？
- Professor Geller?     - Hmm?
喔 一名我不认识的学生
Oh, a student I don't know.
能不能跟您谈一下？
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
当然可以 是哪方面的事？
Yes, of course. What would this be regarding?
- 在你的研究室亲热   - 嘘
- Making out in your office.     - Wh... Shh!
好 我们何不先进去再说
Uh, of course. Why don't we go inside.
嗯...哦
Mm... Oh, oh.
- 怎么了？ - 门把
- What?     - Doorknob. Doorknob.
抱歉 哈哈
Sorry. Ha-ha-ha.
- 我真的有事要讲   - 好 什么事？
- Um, I actually do need to talk to you.     - Oh. Okay, what about?
- 春假的事   - 春假的事？
- Spring vacation.     - Spring vacation?
对 学校没课 很多人要去旅行...
Yeah, we have time off, and a lot of people are going on trips...
- 盖勒教授   - 是 菲森死盯个乐教授...
- Professor Geller.     - Yes, Professor Fiesenstinlender?
我马上就好
I'll be with you in one moment.
那我就买一盒薄荷巧克力饼
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
你们不懂 伊丽莎白想找我跟她去旅行
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
这样叫慢漫来吗？我还没准备好 我该怎么说？
Is that taking it slow? I'm not ready for this, okay?
- 实话实说   - 说你还没准备好
- What do I tell her?     - Tell her the truth. You're not ready.
我可以试试
I could do that.
- 要是她不高兴呢？ - 你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
- Well, what if she gets upset?     - Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
或者
Or...
你也可以...
you could just, you know, you...
你干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
什么
Wha...?
我干什么？你刚弄坏我的冰箱
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
什么？你怎么知道它坏了？
What? How do you know if... How do you know it's even broken?
它怎么坏的我会不知道吗？
Oh, you think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
你等一下
Excuse me.
看吧 坏了
Well, what do you know? Broken!
要赔四百元
That'll be $400.
乔伊 我看见你推他了
Joey, I saw you push him.
是你推的
You pushed him.
乔伊 我没把它弄坏... 它已经坏一阵子了
Joey, I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
- 钱德 我不是提过我们的冰箱的事？ - 嗯哼
- Remember I told you about our fridge?     - Uh-huh.
我还没拿到你该出的钱
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
不要给他钱
Do not give him any money.
你少插嘴 你撞坏我的冰箱
I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
- 盖勒教授 你找我？ - 是的 请进
- You wanted to see me, Professor Geller?     - Yes. Yes. Please come in.
嗯 哦
Mm, ooh, ooh.
- 门把？ - 对 有点玩上瘾了
- Doorknob?     - Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
我想继续上次春假的话题
Actually, I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.
喔 好
Oh, good.
听我说 我...
Look, I...
听着 我跟你在一起很开心
Look, I've been having a great time with you.
我不想进展得太快 或是给我们太多压力
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
所以很抱歉 我们还不能一起旅行
So I'm sorry, I just don't think we should go away together yet.
太快了
It's too soon.
罗斯 你误会我的意思了
Uh, Ross, I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
我只是想告诉你 我要去佛罗里达两星期
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
不
No.
是你误会我的意思了
I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
- 我的意思是...   - 你好可爱
- What I meant was...     - You are so adorable.
这个 我们来讨论这个
That. Let's talk about that.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 你跟伊丽莎白谈得怎样？ - 嗯？哦
- How did it go with Elizabeth?     - Huh? Oh, oh.
没事 只是一场误会 她没有要找我去
Fine. It was just a misunderstanding. She didn't want me to go with her.
她只是要告诉我她要去放春假
She just wanted to let me know that she's going to Florida for spring vacation.
等等 她是去放春假 还是去春游
Wait, is she going for spring vacation or going for spring break.
有什么差别？
What's the difference?
春假是跟爷爷奶奶共享天伦
A spring vacation, you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
春游是跟兄弟会的人上床
Spring break, you're doing frat guys.
并非每个人的春游都那样
Hey, you know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
- 那你做了什么？ - 我跟我爸去埃及
- What did you do on yours?     - I went to Egypt with my dad.
我可以想像 "爸 是人面狮身像"
I can see it now. "Look, Dad, it's the Sphinx."
我想伊丽莎白那么正经 不会去"春游"
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than, "Spring break!"
好吗？她修了我的课
All right? Come on, she's taking my class.
- 还跟教授上床   - 我要去打给她
- And slept with the professor.     - I'm gonna call her.
各位 这是赛巴斯钦
Hey, you guys, I want you to meet Sebastian.
- 嗨   - 我们刚刚
- Hi.     - We just, uh...
在报摊认识 我们都买了《原野与河流》
We just met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream. Ha!
我有在看啊
What, I read that.
- 你要咖啡吗？ - 要 谢谢
- Can I get you a cup of coffee?     - Oh, yes. Thank you.
- 瑞秋 你这是什么意思？ - 什么？
- Rachel, what the hell is this?     - What?
你叫我们帮你找人 却自己带了个人来
You ask us to find you a guy, and then you come in here with a guy of your own.
- 你们帮我找到人了？ - 对
- You found me a guy?     - Yes.
我们在钱德的公司 相中一个可爱风趣的人
We found you a really cute, funny guy from Chandler's work.
我也找了一个不是怪胎的人
Yeah, and I found you one, too, who is not a weirdo.
你们知道吗？真是谢谢你们
You know what though, guys, I really appreciate that...
不过我带赛巴斯钦去就好了
but I'm just gonna take Sebastian to the charity.
你确定？我们这个很香喔
Are you sure? Because our guy smells incredible.
别再提那个了好吗？
Would you stop it with that already?
- 你的咖啡   - 谢谢
- Here you go. Sure.     - Oh, thank you.
赛巴斯钦 你有在当义工吗？
So, Sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?
- 怎么了？ - 没有
- Uh, no, not really. Why?     - No reason.
我只是认识一个关心别人的单身汉
It's just I know a single guy who does care about other people.
你风趣吗？
Are you funny?
- 什么？ -你们在干什么？
- Excuse me?     - What are you guys doing?
你风趣吗？讲个笑话来听
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
Look, I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
很多人都想
Well, so do a lot of people.
- 说实话 我该走了   - 哦 但你...
- Actually, uh, I gotta get going.     - Oh, but you...
- 有空打电话给我   - 你没给我电话号码
- Give me a call sometime.     - But you didn't give me your number.
好 那就改天见
Okay, see you later.
原来他蛮风趣的
Turns out he is kind of funny.
你们真是太扯了
I cannot believe you guys!
他人很好 却被你们赶走了
He was really nice and he just left because of you!
"赛巴斯钦"耶？那是猫的名字吗？
Yeah, but, "Sebastian"? What is that, a cat's name?
你知道我发现什么？他很容易被吓到
You know what I noticed, Rachel, he scares easy.
你想带这种人参加舞会吗？
Now, is that the kind of guy you want to take to a ball?
"赛巴斯钦 要不要跳舞"
"Sebastian, would you like to dance?"
"好 我得走了"
"Uh, okay. I gotta go. Aah!"
别再说了 瑞秋 对不起
All right, guys stop it. Rachel, we're very sorry.
我们太过分了
That is a very insensitive thing for us to do.
这样吧 让我们补偿你 我们有两个好男人让你挑
You know what? Let us make it up to you. We've two great guys for you.
对啊 你有什么损失？
Yeah, what have you got to lose?
搞不好会认识让你心动的人 如果你选我这边的人的话
You might even end up with someone really special. If you pick my guy.
- 好吧   - 好 你愿意见我们找的人？
- All right.     - Okay. So you will meet our guys?
我愿意
Yes, I'll meet them.
你要选谁都行 由你自己决定
It doesn't matter which one you choose. It's up to you.
我们这个才更完美
Our guy is perfect.
或者你也可以选 菲比自己
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed...
- 看不上眼的人   - 啊哦
- not good enough to go out with herself.     - Ugh!
菲比 你在这里 你弄坏我的冰箱
Phoebe, there you are! Okay, you broke my fridge.
欠我四百元
You owe me 400 bucks.
- 好吧   - 真的？
- Okay, sure.     - Really?
技术上来说你欠我六百元
Ooh, technically, you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...
你最近十次试镜我都有祝祷
on your last 10 auditions.
那就算扯平了？
Call it even?
好吧
Okay.
回来了 伊丽莎白怎么说？
There you are. So, what did Elizabeth say?
她真的是要去德通纳春游 呼呼
Well, turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break, woo-hoo."
也就是有湿恤美女选拔赛 男生朝女生身上扔水球
That means wet T-shirt contests, guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
在陌生人身边醒来
waking up next to people you don't even know.
她会玩得很爽
Man, she is gonna have a great time!
她要住可乐娜饭店吗？
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
- 你熟那里的饭店？ - 当然 我参加过81年春游 呼呼
- You know the hotels?     - I was there, Spring Break '81!
81年你才13岁
In 1981, you were 13.
那又怎样？我开车去卖了恤 玩得好开心
So what? I drove down, sold T-shirts. I had a blast.
你们知道谁最会疯？酒醉的大学女生
You know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
好 她不准去
Okay, she can't go.
罗斯 你不能叫她不准去 你们才交往没多久
You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
- 那我该怎么办？ - 不怎么办 你只能接受
- Then what am I supposed to do?     - Nothing. Just be cool with it.
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢？
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
那这次你就别娶她
Well, maybe you don't marry this one.
你能去旅行真是好事
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.
就是啊 我这学期那么用功
Yeah, I've been working so hard this semester.
很需要疯狂下 好解压力
I really need to go crazy, you know? Blow off some steam.
当然
Sure. Sure.
我不知道你的计划到底定了没
Look, I don't know if your plans are finalized yet...
但我知道 还有一个办法可以好解压力
but I know another great way to blow off steam.
- 什么办法？ - 你喜欢做手工艺吗？
- What?     - Are you into crafts at all?
- 罗斯 你还好吗？ - 我当然很好
- Ross, are you okay?     - Uh, yeah. Of course I'm okay.
我只是在表示支持
Heh, I'm just being, uh, supportive.
支持你和这次旅行
Supportive of you and this whole trip...
还有这是什么？
and what... What is, uh...? What's this?
- 那是泳衣   - 你要穿它去见人？
- It's a bathing suit?     - To wear in front of people?
- 这样叫支持吗？ - 这样是吗？
- Is that supportive?     - Is this?
- 嘿   - 太好了
- Hey.     - Good, good, good.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
- 很高兴你答应见我们找的人   - 哦
- We're glad you decided to meet our guy.     - Oh.
你一定会很喜欢他
You're gonna like him so much.
- 你要什么时候见他？ - 不晓得
- Uh, when do you want to meet him?     - I don't know.
- 我知道我明晚不用加班   - 明晚不错
- I don't work late tomorrow night.     - Tomorrow night is good.
不过现在能做的事 为什么要拖到明天？
But why put off something till tomorrow that you can do right now. Ha-ha-ha.
- 艾达 过来   - 什么？
- Eldad, come here!     - What?
- 艾达 这位是瑞秋   - 你好吗？
- Eldad, this is Rachel.     - How are you?
有点措手不及 不过我很好
A little blind-sided, but, you know, good.
艾达 坐...你坐过去
Eldad, sit down. Move over. Move over now.
这就对了
There you go. There you are.
- 好 我们知道了   - 哈哈哈
- Okay, we can take a hint!     - Ha-ha-ha.
- 等等 你来干什么？ - 这位是派屈克
- Wait. What are you doing here?     - This is Patrick.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
你来晚了 她跟我们那个在一起了
You're too late, because she's already with our guy.
天哪 我是来晚了 他们正坐在沙发上聊天
Oh, my God, you're right, I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
过来
Come on.
- 瑞秋 这是派屈克   - 怎样？
- Rachel? This is Patrick.     - Yeah?
- 喔 嗨   - 嗨
- Oh. Hi.     - Hi.
他就是我说的那个人
This is the guy I was telling you about.
相信我 这套西装 太委屈底下的身材了
Believe me, this suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
好
Okay.
但是菲比 我现在正在忙
But Pheebs, I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
好 没关系 你坐
Oh, okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
- 你不能这样   - 我走好了
- You can't do that!     - Maybe I should go.
坐下 我们占上风
Just sit down, we're winning.
也许我才应该走
Okay, you know what? Maybe I should go.
- 不要   - 坐下
- No, no!     - Have a seat!
瑞秋 你还没模过艾达的头发
Rachel, you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
- 超柔顺的 你模模看   - 不必了
- It is the softest hair. Touch it.     - I'm good.
瑞秋 派屈克很有钱 拿钱给她
Rachel, Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
菲比 这个免费按摩的代价太高了
Phoebe, this isn't really worth the free massage.
没错 派屈克 再见
That's right, Patrick. Bye-bye.
艾达合作多了 而且很会跳舞
Eldad is much more cooperative and he can dance.
你跳舞给瑞秋看
You dance for Rachel.
不 拜托不要
No, don't dance for me, please!
你们是怎么搞的？
What is the matter with you guys?
没错 大家来说清楚
Yeah, okay, let's talk it out.
只有我觉得尴尬吗？
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
- 我也有点尴尬   - 嘘
- I'm a little embarrassed.     - Shh, shh.
该尴尬的是你们 这实在是太扯了
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys. This is ridiculous!
很谢谢你们 但我不需要你们帮我找人
Thank you, but I do not need you to get me a date.
- 那你为什么叫我们...   - 我还没说完
- Then why did she ask us to help...     - I am still talking!
你们还把我真正喜欢的人赶走
Then you chase away the one guy that I actually liked.
我没有冒犯的意思 真的 恭喜你有
No offense to you guys. Really, congratulations on...
那么多现金
all the cash.
还有你...你的头发真的很柔顺
And you really... Wow, you do have very soft hair.
但我宁可自己一人参加晚会 也不要再受这种气
But I'd much rather go to the ball by myself than go through any more of this!
再见
Goodbye.
你有用什么特别的润发乳吗？
Now, do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
- 有 木瓜粹取液   - 谢谢
- Yes, papaya extract.     - Thank you.
- 好好去玩吧   - 我会的
- So, uh, have a great time down there.     - I will.
- 你有带那套泳衣吗？ - 有
- Did you pack that bathing suit?     - Yeah.
我刚才把它藏起来 实在蛮好玩的
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while, huh?
总之...
Anyway. Um...
我不是担心那套泳装太曝露
I am worried about that bathing suit.
这一点我不在意
Not because it's revealing, which I'm fine with.
我是关心你的健康
No, I'm concerned about your health.
怕你晒到
Um, sun exposure.
放心 我带了一大堆防晒油
Oh, don't worry, I have plenty of sun block.
- 防晒指数30   - 好的
- It's SPF 30.     - All right.
如果真的有30就好了
Well, if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
有时候是30 有时候只有4 我发誓
I mean, sometimes you get 30, sometimes it's 4, and I swear...
有很多都只是牛奶
more often than not, it's just milk.
罗斯 你放心
Ross, it's gonna be okay.
我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
我真的很喜欢你 我喜欢我们的关系
I really like you. I like how things are going between us.
- 真的？ - 对
- Really?     - Yeah.
我只是跟朋友们去玩玩
I'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
好吧
Okay. Cool. Heh.
- 喔 他们来了   - 嘿 伊丽莎白
- Oh, here they are.     - Hey, Elizabeth!
再见
Bye!
打电话给我
Call me!
瑞秋 抱歉把那些人硬塞给你
Rachel, we're sorry for pushing those guys on you.
没关系 结果我玩得很开心
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
晚会很成功 募到很多款 引起很多重视
The charity was a big success, they raised a lot of money and awareness.
它到底是为什么慕款？
So, what was it for, anyway?
我很想说是一种疾病
I wanna say a disease.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
罗斯留了奇怪的留言 叫我们看MTV台
I just got this weird message from Ross. He said turn on MTV. I don't know.
- 看 是伊丽莎白   - 哈哈哈
- Oh, my God, look! That's Elizabeth!     - Ha-ha-ha.
喔...盖勒教授
Oh, oh, Professor Geller.
重温13岁旧梦 是啊
Ah, to be 13 again.